thai.lt 2019-03-23

# Privacy Policy | THAI.LT

_Last updated: 8 January 2019_

MB Proesna (“us”, “we” or a similar construction) operates the THAI.LT website (the “Website”). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use the Website and the choices you have associated with that data. We use your data to provide and improve the Website.

 ** _By using the Website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy_**.

Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

### Information Collection and Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve the Website.

### Usage Data

We may collect information how the Website is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's IP address, browser type, browser version, the pages of the Website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

### Tracking Cookies Data

THAI.LT (“the Website”) uses cookies - small files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your browsing experience. This page describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored. However, blocking cookies may downgrade or 'break' certain elements of the Website’s functionality.

You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of this site. Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.

For more general information on cookies see [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

#### The Cookies We Set

In order to provide you with a great experience on the Website we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how the Website runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences.

#### Third Party Cookies

In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.

This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solutions on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.

For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the [Google Analytics: Safeguarding Your Data](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html).

We also use third party advertisements on the Website to cover the expenses of running the service. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on the Website, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense service) information including your IP address, your ISP and the browser you used to visit the Website. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. The Google AdSense service we use to serve advertising uses a DoubleClick cookie to serve more relevant ads across the web and limit the number of times that a given ad is shown to you.

For more information on Google AdSense see the official [Google AdSense privacy FAQ](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/3394713?hl=en).

We also use social media buttons and plugins on the Website that allow you to connect with your social networks in various ways. If you share any content on the Website through social networks (for example by clicking a Facebook “like” button or a “Tweet” button) you may be sent cookies from these websites. We do not control the setting of these cookies so please check the websites of these third-parties for more information about their cookies and how to manage them:

Comment feature on the Website is presented via third-party software “Disqus” that uses cookies to allow users to comment on the Website. Please check the website of “Disqus” for more information about their cookies and how to manage them here: [Disqus Privacy Policy](http://help.disqus.com/customer/portal/articles/466259-privacy-policy)

#### Links to Other Websites

The Website may contain links to other websites that are operated by third parties. We don’t control these third party websites (including whether or not they store cookies) and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. Please consult the terms and conditions and Privacy Policy of the relevant third party website to find out how that site collects and uses your information and to establish whether and for what purpose they use cookies.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### More Information

Hopefully that has clarified things for you and as was previously mentioned if there is something that you aren't sure whether you need or not it's usually safer to leave cookies enabled in case it does interact with one of the features you use on our site. However, if you are still looking for more information, then you can contact us through our [Contact Form](https://www.thai.lt/contact-us "Contact Form").
